https://hotdipgalvanizing.com/privacy-statement

News Center
Careers
1-800-801-3648
COMPANY Overview
V&S Galvanizing is a galvanizing service provider that believes in safely doing what we say we’ll do.
HOT-DIP GALVANIZING Overview
V&S Galvanizing is a galvanizing service provider that believes in safely doing what we say we’ll do.
PRIVACY STATEMENT
This web site and its contents ("Web Site") are owned and operated by Voigt & Schweitzer®  of 987 Buckeye Park Road, Columbus, OH 43207, USA. (V&S) This policy (the "Privacy Policy") describes the way in which Voigt & Schweitzer® manages personal information about you obtained by Voigt & Schweitzer® from your use of the Web Site.
By using this Web Site you acknowledge that you have read and understood this Privacy Policy and agree with and consent to the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not consent to these practices you should immediately cease using the Web Site.
The Web Site may be updated from time to time, including this Privacy Policy. Voigt & Schweitzer® encourages you to check this document regularly. By continuing to use this Web Site after this Privacy Policy has been updated, you acknowledge that you have read and understood the updated Privacy Policy and agree to be bound by it.Privacy and personal informationVoigt & Schweitzer® is committed to protecting the privacy of individuals' personal information. Voigt & Schweitzer® will only collect personal information over this Web Site and use, disclose and store that personal information in accordance with the Act and this Privacy Policy. "Personal information" means information or an opinion (including information or an opinion forming part of a database), whether true or not, and whether recorded in a material form or not, about a person whose identity is apparent, or can be reasonably ascertained, from the information or opinion.Collection of personal information Voigt & Schweitzer® may, from time to time, collect and use personal information. The types of personal information Voigt & Schweitzer® collects from you depends upon how you use the Web Site. Generally speaking however, Voigt & Schweitzer® may collect and store any personal information which you enter into the Web Site or which relates to your use of the Web Site. Disclosure of personal informationVoigt & Schweitzer® will not disclose personal information about you collected through the Web Site to third parties except:
where third parties appointed by Voigt & Schweitzer® require access to personal information held by Voigt & Schweitzer® to perform services (in these cases, Voigt & Schweitzer® requires these contractors to keep that personal information confidential and not to use or disclose it for any purpose other than the purpose of performing those services);to any related organizations of Voigt & Schweitzer® in accordance with the law; Voigt & Schweitzer® is required or authorized by law to disclose personal information, for example to law enforcement agencies; or with your consent.
Access to personal informationYou may seek access to personal information which Voigt & Schweitzer® holds about you and Voigt & Schweitzer® will provide access to that information in accordance with the Act. There are certain exemptions which may apply to the provision of that information. Voigt & Schweitzer® may charge an administration fee for granting access to information. To request access to personal information, contact us at the address set out below.
Email DisclaimerDISCLAIMER: E-mails and any files transmitted with them contain confidential and proprietary information and are solely for the use of the intended recipient. If you are not the intended recipient, please return the e-mail to the sender and delete it from your computer. Email transmission cannot be guaranteed to be secure or error-free. The contents of e-mails and any files transmitted with them may have been changed or altered without the consent of the author. Any action taken or omitted to be taken in reliance on the contents of any email or its attachments, is at your own risk, and to the fullest extent permitted by law. Voigt & Schweitzer®  accepts no responsibility or liability to you.
Other issuesThe Web Site contains links to other sites. With the exception of other sites owned by Voigt & Schweitzer®, Voigt & Schweitzer® does not control the privacy practices or policies of sites reached through links from this Web Site. If you have any questions about the privacy practices and policies of those sites then you should contact the companies controlling those sites directly. From time to time, this Web Site may contain chat rooms, message boards, news groups, and other forums. You should be aware than any personal information you disclose on these forums becomes public information, and may be collected and used by others. This may result, for example, in you receiving unsolicited messages from other parties. Nothing in this Privacy Policy guarantees that Voigt & Schweitzer® will collect or store personal information or other information about you and your use of this Web Site. You are responsible for keeping your own records relating to your use of the Web Site and any transactions conducted via it, and for complying with any applicable record keeping legislation.Contact Voigt & Schweitzer®If you have any questions or concerns about Voigt & Schweitzer®’s collection, use or disclosure of personal information, contact us at 987 Buckeye Park Road, Columbus, OH 43207 or by email at info@hotdipgalvanizing.com.
© Copyright 2020 V&S GALVANIZING
TERMS & CONDITIONS
PRIVACY STATEMENT
Locations
News Center
Careers
Standard Terms of Purchase
COMPANY
